https://fastenation.com/privacy-policy/

Created with Sketch.
Created with Sketch.
Updated as of 4/01/20
By using the website www.fastenation.com, (the “Website”) you are knowingly and willingly agreeing to be bound by this Privacy Policy.
We have taken measures to ensure that your online experience with us is safe and secure. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) details the information gathering and sharing practices for FASTENation, Inc. (“Company” or “we”) on the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that we collect offline or through any other means, including on any other websites operated by the Company or a third party. Your access and use of the Website indicates your acceptance of this Policy. Company may change this Policy from time to time, so we encourage you to review our Policy whenever you use the Website to make sure you understand how your information will be used. The Policy, together with our Terms of Use, as may be modified from time to time, govern your use of the Website. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to the Policy will signify your acceptance of the then current Policy. The Policy will include the date we last updated the Policy.
Collection of Information
In general, when you interact with the Website, the Website gathers some generic information from you automatically through the use of log files or otherwise. Generic information does NOT reveal your identity. It includes, but is not limited to, information about the Internet Protocol address assigned to your computer, browser type, Internet Service Provider, platform type, referral source, the number and frequency of visitors and the Web pages visited (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”).
The information that you provide to the Website or that is automatically collected is not sold to other parties. Such information may be disclosed as we deem appropriate in connection with operating and/or providing services through the Website, as detailed in the "Disclosure" section below.
We may store some information on your computer when you access the Website. This information is commonly known as a "Cookie" and once recorded is not accessible by any other company. Cookies are small text files stored by your web browser and sent to a website you visit.  The cookie allows the Website to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Website more useful to you.
We use Cookies in order to better understand how the Website is being accessed and used and Cookies also help us to determine if the Website is being delivered efficiently. In addition, Cookies allow us to enhance your on line experience by customizing your use of the Website and eliminating the need for you to reenter data every time you visit the Website. We also use Cookies to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent uses of the Website or user accounts. The use of Cookies is an industry standard and is used by most major websites to provide the visitor with tailored information.
You should be able to block these Cookies in the first instance, or erase them from your computer after they have been recorded, if you so choose. Please consult the "help" section of your browser or your computer manual  in this regard. You can learn more about cookies at third-party websites such as AllAboutCookies. http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. Please note that if you block or erase these Cookies you may limit the functionality available to you on our Website.
Pages of the Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related Website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).
The Website does not track, collect, or distribute personal information about visitors (such as name, address, email address, telephone number, credit card information or any other information that might reasonably be used to identify visitors personally), except when such information is specifically and knowingly provided by you. Thus, we will only collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, credit card information or any other information that might reasonably be used to identify visitors personally (“Personally Identifiable Information”), when such information is provided to us in an email, on a form, in online survey or in any other manner when this information is intentionally transmitted to the Company by you. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to market products and services from the Website and/or Company that we believe might be of interest to you. Our use of any such Personally Identifiable Information shall be in accordance with applicable laws, rules, and regulations.
Use of Information
Information you provide to the Website will be used by the Company to maintain and improve the services we provide to you, and to provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices.  Information you provide to the Website may also be used to send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages; respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer services; monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our products and services; detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of the Company and others; and to personalize our services, including by providing advertisements, content or features we think will be of interest to you.
Disclosure
We may use Personally Identifiable Information to contact you or to send you news and information about the Website, related products or the Company. We will typically only send you such information if you have opted in or requested to receive such information. To opt out of receiving future mailings, see the Opt Out section below. Company will not knowingly sell or distribute Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for their marketing purposes. If we use third parties to provide specific services or information to you, those third parties may be allowed to use your Personal Information to provide such services. We may share Non-Personally Identifiable Information we collect with our affiliates, contractors and other third parties.
Within Company, your Personally Identifiable Information will be transmitted and stored in a protected environment. We will use commercially reasonable efforts in order not to allow your Personally Identifiable Information to be seen by any third parties other than those that have been engaged by Company to provide services to you including the processing of credit or payments, or for which you have been notified of and provided your consent. We may use Personally Identifiable Information we collect to improve and enhance your overall Website experience. For example, Company may use it to contact you or reply to your requests or send you news and information relating to the Website. In certain circumstances, Company may share Personally Identifiable Information or Non-Personally Identifiable Information when the Company believes it is necessary to comply with the law, court order, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Website and/or any service offered therein or to protect the rights, property or safety of Company’s interests or its customers and you hereby agree to such disclosure. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers or government agencies in connection with fraud protection and credit risk reduction or investigating reports of users using a false email address or users sending or posting harassing, threatening, or abusive messages or other issues related to fraud or government subpoenas, warrants and/or court orders.
Third Party Links and Advertisements
The Website may provide links to other third party websites. Even if the third party is affiliated with Company through a business partnership or otherwise, Company is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only, and you access them at your own risk.
Some advertisements on the Website are served by third-party advertisers, ad networks and ad servers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about users of the Website. This may include information about users' behavior on the Website and other websites to serve them interested-based (behavioral) advertising. We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly.
Opt Out
You may choose to opt out of receiving e-mail messages with news and information about Company or the Website by selecting the Opt Out option available in the e-mail sent to you or by sending an email from the e-mail address at which you are receiving the messages to sales@fastenation.com, requesting that your email address be removed.
Security
We use reasonable security measures designed to protect information about you from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Unfortunately, data transmission over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be secure nor is any security system completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit to the Company or provide online. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All credit card information you provide to us is stored on our or our third party provider’s secure servers behind firewalls and any payment transactions will be encrypted using commercially reasonable technologies. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.
Children Under 13
This Website is not directed at children 13 years of age or younger. Company, therefore, shall not intentionally collect information about any user under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website, make any purchases through the Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at sales@fastenation.com.
California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to sales@fastenation.com.
Contacting Company
You may contact us if you have any questions about this Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with the Website by sending an e-mail to sales@fastenation.com.
×
OK
